<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>

<blog>
	<post>
		<date>March 13, 2023</date>
		<author>Sandra Gonzalez</author>
		<title>Oscar winners 2023: See the full list</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>oscar2023.jpg</image_path>
			<text>for a full list of the nominees.</text>
		</summary>
		<body>BEST PICTURE
        “Everything Everywhere All at Once” *WINNER

ACTRESS IN A SUPPORTING ROLE
Jamie Lee Curtis, “Everything Everywhere All at Once” *WINNER

ACTOR IN A SUPPORTING ROLE
Ke Huy Quan, “Everything Everywhere All at Once” *WINNER

INTERNATIONAL FEATURE FILM
“All Quiet on the Western Front,” Germany *WINNER

DOCUMENTARY (SHORT)
“The Elephant Whisperers” *WINNER

DOCUMENTARY FEATURE
“Navalny” *WINNER

ORIGINAL SONG
“Naatu Naatu” from “RRR” *WINNER

ANIMATED FEATURE FILM
“Guillermo del Toro’s Pinocchio” *WINNER

ADAPTED SCREENPLAY
“Women Talking” *WINNER

ORIGINAL SCREENPLAY
“Everything Everywhere All at Once” *WINNER

ACTOR IN A LEADING ROLE
Brendan Fraser, “The Whale” *WINNER

ACTRESS IN A LEADING ROLE
Michelle Yeoh, “Everything Everywhere All at Once” *WINNER

DIRECTOR
Daniel Scheinert and Daniel Kwan, “Everything Everywhere All at Once” *WINNER

PRODUCTION DESIGN
“All Quiet on the Western Front” *WINNER

CINEMATOGRAPHY
“All Quiet on the Western Front” *WINNER

COSTUME DESIGN
“Black Panther: Wakanda Forever” *WINNER

ACHIEVEMENT IN SOUND
“Top Gun: Maverick” *WINNER

ANIMATED SHORT FILM
“The Boy, the Mole, the Fox and the Horse” *WINNER

LIVE ACTION SHORT FILM
“An Irish Goodbye” *WINNER

ORIGINAL SCORE
“All Quiet on the Western Front” *WINNER

VISUAL EFFECTS
“Avatar: The Way of Water” *WINNER

FILM EDITING
“Everything Everywhere All at Once” *WINNER

MAKEUP AND HAIRSTYLING
“The Whale” *WINNER </body>
	</post>

	<post>
		<date>March 13, 2023</date>
		<author>Mark Savage</author>
		<title>Everything Everywhere All At Once: A guide to the references, Easter eggs and meanings</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>EEA.jpg</image_path>
			<text>At first glance, Everything Everywhere All At Once is not a typical Oscar-winning movie.</text>
		</summary>
		<body>

        1. The plot in a nutshell
        2. There are multiple callbacks to Michelle Yeoh's career
        3. And that's not the only movie reference...  "This movie is one hundred percent a response to The Matrix, obviously," Daniel Kwan said at the South by Southwest festival, where the film premiered. "We wanted to make our version of it."
        4. The movie draws on an Eastern storytelling form called Kishōtenketsu
        5. The visual effects were created by a team of five people
        6. The Ratatouille scenes are more than a throwaway gag
        7. The central message is about the importance of kindness
        8. Pay attention to the bagel

        </body>
	</post>

    	<post>
		<date>January 19, 2023</date>
		<author>Richard Newby</author>
		<title>Why do the Oscars still hate horror movies?</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>horror.jpg</image_path>
			<text>After a banner year for horror in 2022, it's frightening to think that the Academy will likely snub the genre again at next week's Oscar nominations</text>
		</summary>
		<body>
        
       Horror films have never been better. 
       They’ve also never been met with such consistent critical praise.
       So why do the Academy Awards still seem to hate the genre?
       Perhaps hate is too strong a word, but it is evident that the people who vote for the Oscars don’t respect horror in the same way they do every other type of film. 
       Even as voting membership has changed in recent years, with more inclusive representation, there’s been little shift in terms of recognition for one of cinema’s boldest means of storytelling.
       With the 2023 Oscar nominations less than a week away, it’s doubtful the Academy’s bias against horror will change, even though 2022 will be remembered as a historic year for the genre, with films such as X, Pearl, and Nope all earning strong notices from critics and fans while consistently driving some of the year’s best box office performances.

        </body>
	</post>
</blog>
